http://ek-rep.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Warning:
fopen(/homepages/26/d168303642/htdocs/clickandbuilds/EastKilbrideRepTheatreClub/wp-content/plugins/akismet-privacy-policies/languages/akismet-privacy-policies-en_GB.mo): failed to open stream: No such file or directory in /homepages/26/d168303642/htdocs/clickandbuilds/EastKilbrideRepTheatreClub/wp-includes/pomo/streams.php on line 153
Skip to content
East Kilbride Rep Theatre Club
East Kilbride Repertory Theatre Club is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.
East Kilbride Repertory Theatre Club is the Data Controller under the GDPR Data Protection Act 2018, which means that it determines what purposes personal information held, will be used for.  It is also responsible for notifying the Information Commissioner of the data it holds or is likely to hold, and the general purposes that this data will be used for.
Personal information we collect
We will collect information that you supply to us on our website and/or social media accounts.  This may include your name, home address, telephone/mobile number, and email address.
Why we collect this information
We require this information if you contact the club regarding membership application, season ticket application, or general enquiries, or if you leave a comment on any of our pages/posts.
Security
Your personal information will only be processed by East Kilbride Repertory Theatre Club and will not be passed on/sold to a third party.  The information will be stored securely and will only be accessible to authorised members of East Kilbride Repertory Theatre Club.
Analytics/Cookies
We may collect website usage information through site analytics and the use of cookies.  This information does not typically contain information that personally identifies a user.  More information can be found at www.aboutcookies.org.uk.
Links to other websites
Our website currently links to the South Lanarkshire Leisure & Culture Box Office website, and our Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, and YouTube accounts.  We may at any time have links to other websites of interest.  East Kilbride Repertory Theatre Club is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of these websites.
Right of access
All individuals have the right to access, correct, or erase the information East Kilbride Repertory Theatre Club holds about them.  Contact Us.
We reserve the right to change/update this privacy policy at any time.
Last updated: August 2018
facebook
twitter
instagram
youtube
NEXT SHOW: LADIES' DAY - This event has now been cancelled due to current Coronavirus situation.
POSTPONED - NEW MEMBERS RECRUITMENT NIGHT AND WORKSHOP - Wednesday 22nd April, 2020 at 7.30pm - This event has been postponed due to current Coronavirus situation.
Search for:
Search
Categories
EK RepFest (2)
News (1)
Productions (2)
Tweets by @EKRepTheatre
